Yeah, I didn't plan on it. It just kind of
happened. I could sort of kept thinking, well,
I'll go back there someday. And then I realized
it had moved on without me. I keep doing that.
I've done that periodically in my life. I'm
going to write the great American novel. And
um uh actually that that was a mistake. I was
going to just write a novel. And they had this
huge party for me when I left Infocom and they
gave me a t-shirt which I still have which was
the 1989 winner of the Pulitzer Prize which
suddenly put these expectations on it that
um kind of killed that in the bud.
So I'm still interested in it and
I'm still kind of trying to do it but
I've never written that novel. No,
I keep finding other things to do. So I wonder
if I really do want to write the novel or if
I just want to keep dreaming about writing the
novel. There was something to be said for that.